THREE RULES FOR LIVING FROM THE LORD'S PRAYER:
1. Confess all sins to God (Tell it) daily.
2. Surrender your will to God daily.
3. Forgive others and yourself daily.
Dear friend, rule 1 is the key to our success.
When we can't do rule 2 or 3, we must always go to rule 1 and confess it; God will forgive...
We must never stop confessing, even if they are the same old sins we can't seem to stop doing.
As we practice these rules everyday...
God will change our lives.
Also, practice the following little prayer all day:
Lord Jesus, please pour out your mercy, salvation, and deliverance from evil upon everyone I see.
See The Other Side Of This Card For More Help.
Dear friend, if you're not sure where you'll spend eternity, and you want to know now, please pray this simple prayer from the bottom of your heart; as he heard my prayer, He will hear yours also.
Dear Lord Jesus, I understand I am a sinner; I also believe You died for my sins and Your Father in Heaven raised you from the dead.
I simply ask You to have mercy on my life and save my soul.
Come into my heart and my life and take me to Your home someday.
In Your Name Lord Jesus I pray and thank You.
Amen.
For continuous help from God, see other side...
NOTE The spoken credit (not a card line, not a cue): The card's words by brother Daniel · read by a synthesized voice · 3r4l.org — 00:02:08.660